{
  "source": "Monash Questions - Hand Generated",
  "questions": [
    {
      "type": "multichoice",
      "category": "monash",
      "choices": ["Monash Club", "Hargrave-Andrew Library", "New Horizons"],
      "answer": 1,
      "points": 2,
      "question": "Which building occupies the address 13 College Walk, Monash Clayton?"
    },
    {
      "type": "multichoice",
      "category": "monash",
      "choices": [
        "John Monash Science School",
        "Chancellery",
        "North One Carpark"
      ],
      "answer": 2,
      "points": 2,
      "question": "Which building occupies the address 10 Research Way, Monash Clayton?"
    },
    {
      "type": "multichoice",
      "category": "monash",
      "choices": [
        "Sir Louis Matheson Library",
        "Old Science Laboratories",
        "Menzies Building"
      ],
      "answer": 0,
      "points": 2,
      "question": "What at Monash Clayton is Building Four (4)?"
    },
    {
      "type": "multichoice",
      "category": "monash",
      "choices": [
        "Robert Blackwood Hall",
        "Biology - First Year",
        "Menzies Building"
      ],
      "answer": 2,
      "points": 2,
      "question": "Which building occupies the address 20 Chancellors Walk, Monash Clayton?"
    },
    {
      "type": "multichoice",
      "category": "monash",
      "choices": [
        "Religious Centre",
        "Law Building and Library",
        "South-West One Carpark"
      ],
      "answer": 0,
      "points": 2,
      "question": "Which building occupies the address 38 Exhibition Walk, Monash Clayton?"
    },
    {
      "type": "multichoice",
      "category": "monash",
      "choices": [
        "Robert Blackwood Hall",
        "Monash Sport",
        "Sir Louis Matheson Library"
      ],
      "answer": 1,
      "points": 2,
      "question": "What at Monash Clayton is Building One (1)?"
    },
    {
      "type": "multichoice",
      "category": "monash",
      "choices": ["Chancellery", "Performing Arts", "Robert Blackwood Hall"],
      "answer": 2,
      "points": 2,
      "question": "Which building occupies the address 49 Scenic Boulevard, Monash Clayton?"
    },
    {
      "type": "multichoice",
      "category": "monash",
      "choices": ["Monash Club", "Monash Sport", "Campus Centre"],
      "answer": 0,
      "points": 2,
      "question": "Which building occupies the address 32 Exhibition Walk, Monash Clayton?"
    },
    {
      "type": "numeric",
      "category": "monash",
      "answer": 57,
      "points": 3,
      "tolerance": 3,
      "question": "What is Monash's Times Higher Education 2022 World Ranking (to within 3 places)?"
    },
    {
      "type": "numeric",
      "category": "monash",
      "answer": 80,
      "points": 3,
      "tolerance": 3,
      "question": "What is Monash's 2021 Academic Ranking of World Universities (Shanghai) Ranking (to within 3 places)?"
    },
    {
      "type": "multichoice",
      "category": "monash",
      "choices": [
        "The University of Queensland",
        "Monash University",
        "University of Sydney"
      ],
      "answer": 0,
      "points": 2,
      "question": "Which is ranked highest in the Times Higher Education 2022 World Rankings?"
    },
    {
      "type": "multichoice",
      "category": "monash",
      "choices": [
        "UNSW",
        "The University of Queensland",
        "University of Sydney"
      ],
      "answer": 1,
      "points": 2,
      "question": "According to the 2021 (Shanghai) Academic Ranking of World Universities, what is Australia's number two university?"
    }
  ]
}
